const pyquizData = [{
    Question:
        'What is a correct syntax to output "Hello World" in Python?',
    Options: [
        'echo("Hello World");  ',
        'print("Hello World")    ',
        'echo "Hello World"',
        'p("Hello World")',],
    Correct: 1,
}, {
    Question:
        'How do you insert COMMENTS in Python code?',
    Options: [
        '//This is a comment     ',
        '/*This is a comment*/',
        '#This is a comment   ',
        "Don't know",],
    Correct: 2,
}, {
    Question:
        'Which one is NOT a legal variable name?',
    Options: [
        'my_var   ',
        '_myvar',
        'my-var  ',
        'Myvar',],
    Correct: 2,
}, {
    Question:
        'How do you create a variable with the numeric value 5?',
    Options: [
        'x = int(5)  ',
        'x = 5',
        'Both the other answers are correct    ',
        'None ',],
    Correct: 2,
}, {
    Question:
        'What is the correct file extension for Python files?',
    Options: [
        '.pyth   ',
        '.pyt',
        '.pt',
        '.py    ',],
    Correct: 3,
}, {
    Question:
        'How do you create a variable with the floating number 2.8?',
    Options: [
        'Both the other answers are correct     ',
        'x = 2.8',
        'x = float(2.8)',
        'None',],
    Correct: 0,
}, {
    Question:
        'What is the correct syntax to output the type of a variable or object in Python?',
    Options: [
        'print(typeof x)    ',
        'print(typeof(x))',
        'print(type(x))    ',
        'print(typeOf(x))',],
    Correct: 2,
}, {
    Question:
        'What is the correct way to create a function in Python?',
    Options: [
        'def myFunction():   ',
        'function myfunction():',
        'create myFunction():',
        "Don't know ",],
    Correct: 0,
}, {
    Question:
        `In Python, 'Hello', is the same as "Hello"`,
    Options: [
        "Don't know ",
        'True    ',
        'False',
        'None',],
    Correct: 1,
}, {
    Question:
        'What is a correct syntax to return the first character in a string?',
    Options: [
        'x = "Hello"[0]    ',
        'x = sub("Hello", 0, 1)',
        'x = "Hello".sub(0, 1)',
        'None',],
    Correct: 0,
}, {
    Question:
        'Which method can be used to remove any whitespace from both the beginning and the end of a string?',
    Options: [
        'trim()    ',
        'strip()    ',
        'ptrim()',
        'len()',],
    Correct: 1,
}, {
    Question:
        'Which method can be used to return a string in upper case letters?',
    Options: [
        'upper()    ',
        'uppercase()',
        'toUpperCase()',
        'upperCase()',],
    Correct: 0,
}, {
    Question:
        'Which method can be used to replace parts of a string?',
    Options: [
        'switch()    ',
        'replaceString()',
        'replace()    ',
        'repl()',],
    Correct: 2,
}, {
    Question:
        'Which operator is used to multiply numbers?',
    Options: [
        '*     ',
        '#',
        'x',
        '%',],
    Correct: 0,
}, {
    Question:
        'Which operator can be used to compare two values?',
    Options: [
        '><',
        '==  ',
        '<>',
        '=',],
    Correct: 1,
}, {
    Question:
        'Which of these collections defines a LIST?',
    Options: [
        '{"name": "apple", "color": "green"}      ',
        '["apple", "banana", "cherry"]    ',
        '{"apple", "banana", "cherry"}',
        '("apple", "banana", "cherry")',],
    Correct: 1,
}, {
    Question:
        'Which of these collections defines a TUPLE?',
    Options: [
        '["apple", "banana", "cherry"]     ',
        '{"name": "apple", "color": "green"}',
        '{"apple", "banana", "cherry"}',
        '("apple", "banana", "cherry")  ',],
    Correct: 3,
}, {
    Question:
        'Which of these collections defines a SET?',
    Options: [
        '{"apple", "banana", "cherry"}     ',
        '["apple", "banana", "cherry"]',
        '("apple", "banana", "cherry")',
        '{"name": "apple", "color": "green"}',],
    Correct: 0,
}, {
    Question:
        'Which of these collections defines a DICTIONARY?',
    Options: [
        '["apple", "banana", "cherry"]   ',
        '{"name": "apple", "color": "green"}',
        '{"apple", "banana", "cherry"}',
        '("apple", "banana", "cherry")',],
    Correct: 1,
}, {
    Question:
        'Which collection is ordered, changeable, and allows duplicate members?',
    Options: [
        'TUPLE   ',
        'LIST   ',
        'SET',
        'DICTIONARY',],
    Correct: 1,
}, {
    Question:
        'Which collection does not allow duplicate members?',
    Options: [
        'LIST   ',
        'SET   ',
        'TUPLE',
        'None',],
    Correct: 1,
}, {
    Question:
        'How do you start writing an if statement in Python?',
    Options: [
        'if x > y then:    ',
        'if x > y:    ',
        'if (x > y)',
        'None',],
    Correct: 1,
}, {
    Question:
        'How do you start writing a while loop in Python?',
    Options: [
        'while (x > y)  ',
        'x > y while {',
        'while x > y {',
        'while x > y: ',],
    Correct: 3,
}, {
    Question:
        'How do you start writing a for loop in Python?',
    Options: [
        'for each x in y:    ',
        'for x in y:  ',
        'for x > y:',
        'None',],
    Correct: 1,
}, {
    Question:
        'Which statement is used to stop a loop?',
    Options: [
        'stop   ',
        'return',
        'break   ',
        'exit',],
    Correct: 2,
}]
